so today I'm going to explain why I
believe the top is in for the stock
market at
5800 now I'm very confident in that
going into the election here in October
we have topped in the stock market what
I don't know right is how long does this
top last for example you know this top
in the market lasted for 287 days of
downtrend and it took over 700 days
until you took out that high this was a
top it wasn't the forever top right like
this is a top can we all agree on that
okay if you said right here I think the
Market's going to go lower from here
that was a top it lasted for 100 days
and it took over 140 days until you beat
that top again so once again I think
much like this and much like this right
these two points in the chart I think we
are yet again at another top now here's
the question how long does that top last
cuz you know over here lasted 300 days
over here it lasted 100 days this one
could last 50 days could last years okay
but what I'm confident in is this
specific Pivot Point like here like here
and like here that's your top in the
short term which could actually be a
very longterm top and I'm going to
explain why in this video guys I'm going
to show you patterns which could could
lead to our downfall an absolute
destruction of my net worth as you guys
know I hold over $10 million in meme
coins here's just one wallet here where
I have $5.8 million of my favorite meme
coin the cycle which is Brett by the way
to anyone who wants to say over $10
million in meme coins but it's not
liquid bro it's as liquid as your house
if not more liquid if you have a 5.7
million house and you want to sell it
you think you're going to get 5.7
million for it right away hell no you're
going to get undercut you're going to
get low balls it's going to take you
months if not a year or more to sell
your $5.6 million house so if you wanted
to sell your house quickly you'd have
slippage on it same thing with a meme
coin in like this position of Bret I
have here yeah at the moment it's worth
5.8 5.7 with slippage if you want to get
out instantly you don't want to sell you
know slowly gently responsibly
intelligently you're going to lose money
to slip it just like you would on any
transaction really you want to sell your
car fast you're going to have slippage
the fact is I could get myself almost
$3.6 million liquid in a second right
now if I click a couple buttons and you
guys know I have over a million dollars
in multiple other memec coin trades like
Pony like Tron like Pepe so yes guys
when I say I can get7 million plus
dollars out of my meme portfolio liquid
I mean this second should I choose to
sell but I refuse to and you'll explain
exp uh and I'll explain why in this
video everything why even though I just
uh see this being the top in the market
why I'm not selling any meme coins right
now why would I make that decision if I
think it's the top in the stock market
I'm going to go over patterns I'm going
to go over Bitcoin and the way it reacts
to pre-election months for the stock
market guys watch this video it's going
to be long but most likely it's going to
be worth it for you if you're not a
total dork okay watch the video video
okay I think this mcoin when Bitcoin
goes to
$150,000 plus I think you're going to
see this at a 20 billion plus market cap
over a 20x plus here easily that said
you know if the market crashes you can
forget all your bubble predictions and
targets for crypto assets and meme coins
it's not going to happen if the world is
falling apart and the Market's crashing
right same with Bitcoin same with
everything nothing is going to do well
if the market is absolutely crashing
down to something like 3,800
4,000 so what I'm going to do in this
video I'm going to explain to you first
off why am I so confident that this is
the top at the very least for the
shortterm in the market second how this
could actually turn into a very
long-term top that could actually take
us years to recover from so I want to
start off by pointing out to you a
pattern which is the fact that every
single time in September and October the
stock market pretty much tops in uh you
know going into the election so go with
me right here right in
2020 going into the election the market
tops and it drops in September and
October it has a roughly 9 to 10% drop
here in September and it has rough here
another 8 to 9% drop in October so once
again what do I mean by it Tops bro
these are big drops happening going into
the election and you if you're bullish
you're losing money in those months
right obviously depends on your entry
but we can be very clear if you bought
in September October you're not making
money in those months okay now let's go
back to
2016 okay and you will notice the same
thing happened right in 2016
the market does what in September and
October going into the election once
again you do not make a single penny
being bullish on this Market going into
election September October of 2016 what
happens goes down right you can see what
it does going into the election and then
November it bottoms and it's up only
from there okay so two for two right now
you've seen what SE September and
October you don't make a penny if you're
bullish but in November the market goes
up only right you don't make a penny if
you're bullish September October but
November comes around up only and it's
bullish let's keep going so back in 2012
September and October what do you notice
the stock market tops and it drops going
into election and the market Bottoms in
November and starts to make its way back
up and it hits and breaks those highs
only in January to February of the next
year but once again September October
the market tops it drops that is a top
guys okay that is a top it goes down 9%
and it takes a while to recover and make
that new high okay now let's go back to
2008 what happens here same thing
September and October the stock market
is you know you're not making a penny if
you're bullish right obviously it topped
up here but it's also it's topped there
too like you buy in September
October what it is up it is not the
exact top but it's topped right it's
going down if you buy in October what
happens you buy it here and it goes down
how long does it take to recover guys it
first off you drop for 160 days and it
takes you over 470 days to get back to
those levels okay of September October
going into election let's take this
another four years earlier and in 2004
you'll notice this right the same patter
we're getting earlier in recent memory
which is a drop in September a drop in
October so in September here the drop
wasn't so severe but you're not making
money being bullish it drops around 3%
and then in
October okay it drops 4% now this one is
mostly actually just sideways but it's a
volatile right it's like down up down up
but once again in in November the market
goes up only from there okay so you top
in October and you know in this case for
example and and we we won't even call
this a top but I mean it is volatility
going into the election so you set a top
in October and it takes you about 32
days to to see new highs there okay the
thing is about the stock market now is
we're at all-time highs like we are
right at the all-time high basically
okay that's the big difference between
this one and you know the where we're at
currently now let's go back to 2000 what
do you notice same pattern right as
almost every single time going into the
election September and October man it is
not a good time to be a buyer of the
stock market going into the election of
September October and obviously this was
also the.com bubble Soom bubble pops
going into the 2000 election and so what
once again not you don't make a penny
being bullish here okay Market goes much
further uh lower so what do you notice
what I'm trying to show you is that the
S&P 500 nobody ever makes money buying
the S&P 500 basically in the months of
September October going into an election
so I come back over here to the S&P
chart right now which is at all-time
highs
basically and what it always does pretty
much is you don't make any money buying
in October going into election so when I
see something that's at all-time highs
with bearish Divergence right with as
the price is going up in the stock
market volume is decreasing as you can
see here right you can see as the stock
market moves higher the volume is going
down so two bearish divergences here
Market's trying to go higher it's
getting weaker Market's trying to go
higher volume is decreasing and
to top it all off you have this special
pattern that I want to point out and
maybe special is the wrong word to use
but you have this right here top one
okay which I'm going to zoom in on this
with you so you can see what I'm talking
about okay you have and we're going to
make this green okay so you have top one
into top
two into an overshoot into top three
here right and so this this right here
is the exact same pattern you're seeing
happen right now seriously just look at
it side by side and you'll see what I
mean okay so take that there take that
there and take that there same pattern
right once again you have top one top
two overshoot into top three top one top
two overshoot into top three and as well
here you had what bearish Divergence and
you had decreasing
buyers on the way up as you can see
there okay you can see as well here
right price is going up volume is
decreasing okay so you have the same
characteristics that led to a top going
into 2022 which was lowering volume on
the way up with decreasing strength on
the way up two tops into overshoot and a
third top two tops in an overshoot into
a third top decreasing strength and
volume okay so the pattern is the same
as 2022 of course circumstances are
different we're going into election now
but much like 2022 this was an all-time
high setup this was an all-time high top
and this is also going to be an all-time
high top going into the election with
the same pattern same everything besides
we're going to the election but what's
so cool about going into the election
guys is that we see there's a pattern
where every single time go into the
election September and October nobody
makes money being bullish on the market
okay so when you combine all these
factors I have an extreme confidence
that the top is already set in the stock
market it was set at 5,800 we are at the
top basically just barely off the top
right now you know as I've been
recording this video it was at
5756 and it's been dropping while I've
been recording and making this video
this is my second take uh actually
making this video so look now that you
know what where my confidence comes from
on why I believe the top is absolutely
in on this Market what I can't know is
the
duration how long does it take for us to
recover and make a new all-time high
from this top because it could be 60
days you know if you go back and look at
these examples right obviously yes the
market loves to top going into the
election but okay right here for example
and obviously this is no ultimate top or
any major top but like the point is that
you're not making money buying the stock
market going into election and so if we
just look at what's the high in October
obviously here was the shortest time
ever to actually get back to that high
which is about 30 days but if you look
at all these other examples right over
here man holy [__] you know September
October going into election how long
does it take to get back there 2,300
days let's go back to 28 how long does
it take to get back there it takes about
591 days or 800 days depending on you
know the exact measurement there over
here you top going into the election how
long does it take after you top right so
you drop for 70 days and it takes you
another 130 days as you can see you're
not actually making new highs until mid
January late January I'm sorry okay so
this is mid late January making new
highs in the stock market over here
right you're not making new highs in the
stock market post elction until as well
about late December okay so once again
the top is in over here going into the
election and it takes you know 80 100 7
days to make a new high from October
which is where we're at right now right
it takes about you know how long is that
80 days to make a new all-time high so
let's keep it up let's keep going once
again if you say you set the top in
October here
how long does it take to make a new
alltime high about 33 days before you
make a new alltime high and recover in
November so what what am I trying to get
out here first off you ain't going to
make no money buying the stock market in
October and not only just based off of
that tendency which the stock market
likes to do which is top in September
October going into the election right
what that's not including is this
pattern that we're repeating right now
which is a bearish topping pattern with
bearish Divergence with bearish volume
Divergence right so everything lines up
for this to be the top in the short term
here's the thing this could unwind into
a long-term top like we saw in 200000
like we saw in 2008 right the and real
estate
bubble right so this is the thing most
of the time you see what we top in
October and then guess what the market
is up only in November after that but
we've seen in two instances in the last
20 four years that after topping in
October the market unwinds down and the
bubble pops right so this is what I want
people to be aware of this is what I
want people to understand is the market
is
topping we don't know for sure right
whether this will be an easily erasable
dip or could this actually just end up
being a very long-term top of a year
plus it could actually take years before
we ever break this top that's what's so
crazy about this because when absolutely
nobody expects that you could be setting
the ultimate top for a long time also
though once again you know what's
interesting what plays into and ties
into this you know how a lot of people
say well if the Democrats win the
world's going to go to hell and shit's
going to going to get really bad and so
that ties in very well with the 2008
with the 2000 scenario right Kamala wins
and you start to get what take this
pattern over here and you start to get
something like that playing out again
now this is obviously speculation this
is you know this actually this scenario
could happen with Trump winning too
right you got to realize that I'm just
making I'm I'm I'm matching up the
narratives that people are spreading
about the world they're saying hey if
camalo wins you know the Market's going
to go to [__] if Trump wins the Market's
going to be so bullish the reality is
this could actually happen with Trump
winning it could happen with Cala
winning we actually don't understand the
factors happening around the world truly
there's too many factors going on in the
world for you to know like the the the
entire world could collapse and go to
[__] with Trump winning or Cala winning
you don't actually know what you do know
though is that there's an incredibly
High chance that the top is right there
that's what I believe the top is here
what I don't know is that is it going to
be like most of the time where you know
we top and then we we just recover and
go up only in November or we top and the
end of the world starts to come in like
2008 or the dot bubble to me what lines
up very well with this is that yeah if
the Democrats do win this bubble pop
that's the ultimate top for a long time
that nobody is thinking about that right
now no one is expecting that and that
can happen right that starts to make a
lot more sense now if Trump wins well
think about that everyone thinks well
Trump comes in he prioritizes the stock
market Market's going to be so bullish
see if Trump wins that's far more likely
in line with the scenario that we go up
only after November now personally I
don't fall for the propaganda that
people love to spread which is that if
Democrats win that's it the Market's
[__] because because we
saw right when Biden
won um over here in 2020 the market went
up like crazy obviously there were
stimulus checks and it was a crazy
bubble but regardless of Biden and
Democrats winning and you love like
people love to say oh if they win it's
over Market went raging bullish so I
don't buy into that propaganda except
when I actually look at the charts and I
actually look look at how this has
played out for the last 24 years it
seems far more likely that actually a
Democrat win lines up with the end of
the world
scenario now like I said the end of the
world can still come with Trump being
elected
to just know like we can't know with
certainty like all these things in the
future all I can know and have
confidence in is this pattern and the
tendency of the stock market to top
going into the election so what you can
do is be bearish on the stock market
from this point and know that what we
typically do is we recover 45 to 100
days
after to a new all-time high from the
top being set but in 2000 and 2008 we
saw things unwind down way worse so
basically the way I look at it is the
top is in it could take us as soon as we
could be getting back to this all-time
high we could be getting back here in
late November to December to
January but I am very aware that while
no one thinks it's possible while no one
sees it potentially coming the ultimate
top could liter literally just be in you
know um and so obviously no one expected
that in 2008 or in 2000 people were high
off life high off making all their gains
um you know in
2000 no one saw it coming did
they I mean I I know some people saw it
coming but the point is you know we
could be right here you know and I
wouldn't be shocked I really wouldn't
actually be shocked I mean look at the
market it goes up only
forever and um you know it really
wouldn't Shock Me
so what will happen to people like
myself well here's the thing if we get
the typical reaction after an election
which is that the market quickly
recovers starting in November and gets
back to all-time high by end of November
or December January right if we have
just a if this is the top for like one
to three months we're going to be AOK in
crypto okay we're going to be just fine
in
crypto where we're [__] is if this top
is not a short-term top and obviously it
unwinds down into something much more
serious than we thought here's what you
have you know this is the top or at
least I believe with such strong
confidence that's the top I just don't
know if this is going to be that
short-term top or if it's going to be
truly has the potential to unwind in
something way worse than we thought but
the fact that you can even know that
that's the top that's the that's the
takeaway bro how many people can know
with confidence that the top is in you
know I know the top is in I just don't
know how long it's going to last you see
what I'm saying but you know the top is
in like you won't be caught off guard
you won't be surprised you won't be
[__] caught with your pants down
completely you won't be completely naked
totally not seeing this coming from 8
Miles Away potentially you know like
this could be the
top but the typical pattern and tendency
after elections we recover pretty
quickly after so so to
me man I I just obviously I wish I knew
for sure but all I
know is that I believe the top is in and
so you know we'll play it month by month
but I I I I know that minimum I don't we
will not see a new all-time high in the
stock market until late November I
believe okay that's my bet that's what I
can tell you definitively we won't see a
new alltime high I believe until late
November at the
earliest top is in
okay top is in with the potential to be
a short-term top or get into something
much worse than anyone expected uh you
know and so check this out the dollar
right people think okay us is lowering
interest rates meaning the dollar should
weaken right the dollar should go down
if the US is lowering interest rates is
what most people
think obviously there's so many factors
in play in the world um you know like
other countries lowering interest rates
which is actually strengthening the
dollar too but on the surface most
people think well if other countries are
raising their interest rate I'm sorry
lowering their interest rates besides
Japan is is Raising but I think China
what just did the largest rate cut and
their their Market's pumping like crazy
but you know most people here at the
bottom right here were thinking that
this that the dollar was going to break
down and the Bull Run was about to begin
and what does it do it counter counter
trade wins right while everyone thinks
the dollar is going to break down it
pumps up and it's pumping like a
[__] right on this chart so just
keep that in mind this is the bottom of
the range this is the top of the
range
um you know the dollar looks bullish
right now which is overall not good for
the market you know so that is not what
you want to see for a the big bull
market that everyone's preparing for so
obviously once you start to break down
that's when you're really in my opinion
in a confirmed bull run like the the
euphoric beautiful part of the bull run
where you make stupid money easily in
crypto but right now dude everyone
thought the dollar was going to break
down it's not breaking down you should
see my messages with people you should
see I called this out in my telegram I
said everyone and their mothers is
loading up Max bullish right now
everyone thinks the dollar is going to
break down and the Bull Run begins and
everyone and their mothers is screaming
for
October now I entered a short position
here luckily I'm up around
$260,000 on the short but once again man
I am making way more money when the
market goes up believe me I am losing my
ass when the market goes down thank God
I could hedge a little bit and make a
little bit on the short side but believe
me I will lose way more money if the
market goes down than I will make on
this short so obviously you know I'm not
positioned the best right now but you
know at least I got a hedge there and I
got a hedge on another account but the
point is is to not be caught completely
off guard if things got way worse than
you expected from this specific top cuz
man tops happen like top tier we Dro for
two years almost or one year and then
two years to recover right top tier it
takes us 100 you know how many 100 4 40
days to recover it's like when you have
a top you know dude it could of course
we could recover in 50 days it could
also take us a long time to recover are
you prepared for that now you know the
Market's just been going up only so
easily it's like you guys forget that
hey man crashes and some strong
Corrections do happen like obviously you
had covid here okay and from the covid
crash it took you another six 690 days
until the next crash now how many days
has it been since our last crash in top
it's been a, days without a true major
crash like guys we've went plenty of
time without a without a you know a due
correction like a serious one like Co
like that one like if you don't think we
could get one here over the next six to
12 months like look man it can easily
happen and the worst thing you can do
is be horribly horribly horribly
positioned thinking that that's not even
a possibility I'm telling you like the
top is here and it could unwind into
being way worse than anyone is expecting
it could also just be like a 50-day top
and we'll be okay like you know that's
what I'm trying to to to make the point
of you know
so yeah um let's see how obviously you
had this top into a drop
in 2008 and you know you went up after
the after horrible pain you have very
little pain for a long time you know and
it took
us 4500 days until the next major major
crash I mean you could say this is a
major crash though you know I mean 15%
is pretty big you know these are some
big crashes but honestly they look small
no but those are actually pretty big it
just looks small because this was so big
so yeah um never mind let's do this from
from this crash to the next crash 900
days from that crash right to that crash
days from this crash to the next one you
could say 350 days and this crash wasn't
the worst right 11% so it's just like
man if you don't think guys we
went 900 days since you know the last
serious downtrend or like pullback like
dude it that was not a bad time whenever
you have this tendency of topping before
the election you have a potential Camala
win you have a lot of people who are
probably going to want to drisk going
into the election because they're
uncertain of who's going to win right
the market's at alltime highs you got
bearish diver you got bearish volume
Dage you got so many factors and so much
logical reasoning for why makes sense
for this to top at
5800 once again do we recover in 50 days
or within years that's the part we don't
know for a fact right now but the common
tendency once again is after the
election in November we usually go up
only so it does make sense that the
Trump Victory is far more in line with
us recovering and being good from
November and Beyond and the Democratic
Victory would go very well in line with
a things get way worse than anyone or
most people are expecting and we get
[__] so here's the good news um
somewhat is that in all the
situations where the stock market topped
in October going into election but
quickly recovered in November or
December or January and all those cases
pretty much uh you know Bitcoin was has
been unaffected by the volatility going
into the election
uh and so you know if if the market
recovers quickly after this election and
it's hopefully a trump Victory then
we're good so once again this is the top
it's just we can't really know the
severity or at least I don't right now
of the consequences of this top right
once again is just a shortterm you know
50-day to 150 day top or does it unwind
down way worse here's the thing if
crypto shows rength through the
pre-election volatility I'm going to be
led to believe that it is doing what
it's always done and that the market is
going to strongly recover after the
election now if crypto is selling off
like a [__] with the volatility
and it's reacting horribly with the
volatility that to me is going to be a
sign of weakness why because every other
election that Bitcoin has been around
for pre-election that pre-election
volatility of the stock market barely
affected Bitcoin it was actually Bitcoin
did great in those moments so if we see
pre-election Bitcoin is doing [__] here
that's your bad sign but if it just
holds up and does solid that's a good
sign that's what we're looking out for
here right now for crypto so what's
performing good in my eyes through
pre-election stock market volatility is
if ethereum just hangs out down here man
without breaking down like it hanging
out down here while the stock market's
going ham while people are unwinding
positions before the election that's so
bullish right uh Bitcoin hanging around
where it is meanwhile all that
pre-election stock market volatility is
going and people are nervous unwinding
down their positions based on which
candidate is going to win is going to
affect the outcomes and results of a lot
of stocks and how they perform over the
next four years right so once again the
more chill these hold up the less they
react to stock market volatility the
more I'm going to be led to believe that
man everything is totally fine we're
going to continue this bull run like
we've all planned and
expected but yeah I hope that makes
sense man I I I hope although don't you
know realize man this you know World
falls apart scenario can happen with
Trump or Camala winning I hope you guys
realize that right like if a Domino's
going to fall it's not like Trump can
just like save the world from collapsing
you realize there's so many factors in
the world and the United States is not
the only one right so keep that in mind
either presidential candidate could lead
to a
crash so anyways I think I've explained
myself here for the most part um what
I'm so confident in is that the top is
in shortterm and that short-term top
could turn into a long-term top that's a
part I don't know right now but you know
I want credit for seeing a major crash
coming from a mile away should it come
but obviously once again the the comment
tendency quick recovery after the
election so just know that this is the
top though for now I believe and I I'll
stand by that and if I'm wrong I
apologize I can't read the future but I
can only make my best guesses and try to
predict it and I have a pretty damn good
track record of it and I was really
happy to make this video and you know I
don't really make videos often but
sometimes things get me excited and
being able to potentially see something
like that come you know just having a
overall just a definitive confidence
that the top is in for the stock market
and we could have a quick recovery or a
horrible you know long recovery but at
least I I'm confident that the top is in
I'm not some idiot buying the top right
now you know what I mean that makes me
happy um and so last thing I should say
though is obviously look Bitcoin was
completely
unaffected here with through all the
stock market volatility going into the
election Bitcoin was unaffected and
going high right you can see that here
unaffected during look at this this is
crashing and look look up look up
bitcoin's going
up let's go back over here to uh 2016
right you'll see again it's not loading
here I think that's cuz that's
binance uh Bitcoin was unaffected so
that's the good news is since bitcoin's
been alive any stock market volatility
pre-election has not really affected it
too negatively at all actually it's been
able to hold up really well going into
these elections so you know basically
summary here is if that you know we get
an
extended you know a top within a very
extended correction hey Bitcoin
everything you know is going down okay I
believe uh because and by the way how
would I think that cuz gold
gold went
down um a lot when the 2008 financial
crisis hit right so let's go back here
to Gold it [__] the bed right and then
obviously up only and it performing you
know really well after the crash but you
know gold went down in a financial
crisis so I think Bitcoin will as well
that's what you need to know in my
opinion so if you have a financial
crisis or some really bad [__] world
falling apart expect Bitcoin obviously
to [__] the beds Your Meme coins
everything but at least you'd be
somewhat ready for it but also at the
same time look the common tendency once
again quick recovery in November
starting in November you start to get
back to that all-time high by end of
November December January so anyways
tops in bro drop a like make sure you
subscribed hopefully you understand that
our advantage is at least in stock man
you're not buying the [__] top right
now because you're confident this is the
top so you wouldn't be buying it you
know there's people out there in the
world who are buying this [__] at the
[__] top why would you do that of
course yes we can recover you know earli
in my opinion 50 days from now but I
ain't going to be buying the [__] top
you know and you know rest in peace to
the soldiers that do hopefully the
market recovers within 50 days for them
at the early in my opinion but yeah you
know you're prepared and um you know I
said on Twitter that I'll be giving
myself two chances to call the top in
stocks the cycle one of these chances I
will use here in October 2024 for all
the reasons I've shared and yeah
basically
though I said for now going into
election this is the top I believe but
in 2020 2016 2012 crypto was completely
unaffected by the shaky stock market
going into election I'm confident this a
short-term uh top in stocks at the
moment a one three months top in stocks
we'll be fine for crypto right we'll be
fine if it's just a one to three month
top we should be fine where this hurts
us badly as crypto holders and people
that all the [__] in in
crypto is if this top that we see here
ends up being the ultimate top and not
just the 50 to 150 day top you know so
we're going to be watching that and I'll
try to keep you updated make sure you
follow me on Twitter but that's what I'm
looking at right now and once again just
have relief to not being buying the top
of the stock market right now which is
what I believe it is and um obviously
once again if it's just a one to three
month correction in the stock market I
think crypto is going to be fine if it
extends beyond that that's where we're
[__] so final words on this this video
is not to scare you if anything it's to
prepare you just in case to you know be
warned that this is the top short term
at the very least of course it could
turn into something worse than that but
will I be selling my meme coins
absolutely not here's the thing I stand
by the fact that I think Bitcoin is
going to be trading at above
$150,000 in the next few years you know
I mean few years is if that happens and
in the reality in the next year or two I
believe Bitcoin will be trading above
130 150k if that happens I'm going to
make 20x plus minimum on Meme coins now
20x plus will change my life
man you know losing 50% will not I'll be
fine keep that in mind also though is I
believe we should be able to see if
crypto maintains a strength despite a
market top being in on the stock market
that would be showing us the
characteristics of the previous times
where Bitcoin has been completely
unaffected right remember the last three
times Bitcoin was completely unaffected
affected by the volatility so if we see
volatility in the stock market and
Bitcoin is pretty much minimally
affected over the next month or two then
that to me would be a very good sign
that it's like the other times where
Bitcoin was unaffected so what I want to
see now is look stock market be as
volatile as you want I want to see
Bitcoin be minimally affected by the
volatility of the stock market going
into election if it does that then we're
on track to be doing what we've always
done now if Bitcoin is reacting horribly
to the volatility in the stock market
and [__] the bed with the stock
market you know being volatile that's a
bad sign that the entire Market is weak
so that's how I'm looking at this right
now so once again I will not be selling
any of my meme coins what I'm going to
be doing I'm going to be waiting and
watching to see that this lines up with
how we've always been uh playing out in
Bitcoin in the past three elections so
yeah hopefully that makes sense drop a
like make sure you subscribed remember
20x plus higher in meme coins when
bitcoin's a two and a/x higher that can
change your life being down 50% man you
know you can argue oh what if I sell and
buy back in lower but what if you sell
and you don't buy back in lower was it
worth missing out on a 20x plus to try
and buy back in you know lower I mean
I'm not going to lie this would be end
of the world but and man you're probably
[__] either way if if that happens so
you know I would personally I'm thinking
about the life-changing upside that is
very easily there and once again
tendency is that we recover after the
election pretty pretty easily usually so
and by the way you know obviously I've
been so freaking bullish on bitcoin
since 15K and I still am I still have
the same belief that we're going to see
Bitcoin above 150k it's inevitable the
thing is the whole way up I've been so
bullish as a stock market has also been
but this is what a lot of you should
realize I am not a je who is like oh no
the stock market is crashing now I'm
going to be possibly bearish no no no I
am scared for all of us at the what I
believe could easily be a top right what
I believe is shortterm it's a minimum at
shortterm a top that could unwind into a
longer term top you see there's a
difference between getting scared of a
top at the top and and instead of where
what people do is they turn bearish
after shit's
dropping okay I am getting scared for
others when [__] is pumping right when
[__] is at the [__] Peak going into
the election I think that's a time to be
incredibly cautious of course once again
we've seen that even when the stock
market goes down going into election
Bitcoin has been able to hold up fine
the last you know you know what's it
been decade so let's hope that remains
the case and if that's Remains the case
we're going to be looking good of course
once again if things unwind down longer
and worse than we expected don't expect
Bitcoin to hold up in in a horrible
situation like that and man forget your
your magic internet money bro you're not
going to be making money in crypto or in
stocks or in anything unless you know
how to short and even then you're really
going to Short your whole net worth hell
no you know we hedge you know I got a
little hedge but you're crazy if you
think I'm going to put my net worth on
the short side I'm putting my net worth
on the [__] bull side cuz that's
where the most money is going to be made
always even if you got to hold through a
financial crisis or or any [__] that was
unexpected the real money you know the
meme coins and [__] can go up 20x plus
the market can go down you
know 30% is considered as bad as it gets
pretty much in the stock market you know
um well recently at least in the last
couple decades so yeah I mean the upside
is always going to be way more in your
favor on the bull side so I mean all I
can do is is hedge and and really hope
for the best but you know I'm not I'm
not sacrificing my positions at all on
the bull side no [__] way man um I'm
just going to try to make as much money
as I can if we do you know if the stock
market were to be worse than expected
but dude I could be totally overreacting
and over worried right now that's what
you got to understand that we could be
totally fine like I said November comes
we recover like we always do and none of
this [__] matters but you just cannot
be surprised if the short-term top
actually did turn into a long-term top
man I wouldn't be surprised that's why I
had to spend [__] over 40 minutes
talking about this man cuz that that
could be crazy that could wipe out so
many people fortunes lives so many
people could be so [__] if they didn't
see this coming and you know when you
have reason to see and believe that man
something of that caliber magnitude
could actually hit and you have
sufficient reasons and and tendencies in
the charts that are there to support
that actually being a real possibility
man it would suck for you to be on the
complete wrong side or not even be
thinking about it you know and like I
said okay so the last 24 years of
presidential elections two of them led
to massive collapses and what three to
four of them we recovered totally fine
right after in November you know but
yeah I mean the last two major [__]
crashes outside of Co happened you know
election year so keep that in mind man
all right